# Joseph Oluwadara

#### BLOCKCHAIN SECURITY ENGINEER

jsatimehin@gmail.com Github LinkedIn Twitter Website

## **PROFILE**

I am a self taught Smart Contract Engineer and Auditor, experienced in writing and auditing Solidity smart contracts. With a deep understanding of the EVM and Solidity, I have written and audited complex, efficient and secure smart contracts, compatible with EVM L1s and L2s.

Some of my favorite tools include:

- 1. Foundry, Hardhat and Remix for smart contract writing, testing, fuzz testing and fork testing against live blockchain instances.
- 2. Automated tools Slither and Echidna from static testing.

I have experience auditing and writing different smart contracts including: AMMs, Fungible and Non Fungible tokens, Sales contracts, Auction contracts, Liquidity staking contracts, Account Abstraction Wallets, Vaults, Factories, Proxies and Upgradeable contracts.

I currently do smart contract audits at Code4rena, Sherlock and ImmuneFi. I also participate in different CTFs and I have completed a few such as Ethernaut from Openzeppelin, Damn Vulnerable Defi, Secureum Bootcamp and more.

#### Some of my skills include:

- Solidity
- Assembly: YUL
- Foundry
- Hardhat
- EthersJS
- Slither
- JavaScript
- Typescript
- NodeJS
- Graph
- Rust
- NextJS & React

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Smart Contract Auditor**

April 2023 - Present

- Participated in the Stader Labs Audit contest at Code4rena with 2 Rewarded findings.
- Participated in the PopsicleFinance Audit contest at Sherlock with 2 Rewarded findings.
- Participated in the IronBank Audit contest at Sherlock with 2 Rewarded findings.
- Found Bugs in two projects listed on ImmuneFi, [Cannot Be Disclosed Yet].
- Participated in the Secureum Bootcamp RACE.
- Completed one Private Audit.

All bugs rewarded so far are High/Medium. Low/Non-Critical/Gas Optimization reports are usually unrewarded, but I submit them, for no rewards.

At the time of submission of this resume, I have 5 pending results from both Code4rena and Sherlock with valid findings in them.

# Blockchain Developer (Contract)

#### Astra Metaverse

September 2022 - January 2023

- Created an ERC 1155 token smart contract and minter
- Created a Metaverse Marketplace smart contract
- Writing APIs to connect with the smart contracts on the blockchain

# Blockchain Developer

#### **COLLECT WAVES**

May 2022 - December 2022

- Created & Tested an Music NFT smart Contract
- Designed an NFT market place smart contract and NFT minter
- Writing APIs to connect with the smart contracts on the blockchain
- Creation of Tokens.

# FullStack Blockchain Developer

## LivingStone Blockchain IT

January 2022 - August 2022

- Writing and testing smart contracts on the EVM compatible blockchains
- Building a UI that interacts with the blockchain with web3.js
- Created a Decentralized Exchange to swap tokens
- Interviewed and lead the daily activities of a team of Developers

# Frontend Solutions Developer

#### IPI SOLUTIONS

May 2021 - February 2022

- Built a Document Management System around Microsoft Sharepoint using Angular and Typescript
- Created and Modified 3000+ Document Libraries

# **EDUCATION**

# BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, MATHEMATICS

Federal University of Abeokuta, Ogun, Nigeria.

2018 - 2022